OLATUNJI AYOBAMI

Frontend Developer (React.JS)

SUMMARY

A FrontEnd developer with 3 years+ development and production experience with HTML, CSS, Javascript, ReactJS and the technology built around it like React, Webpack, Enzyme, Redux, and Flux. I also have successfully used these technologies in building some real-world projects which can be found in my GitHub repositories and my portfolio. I love to convert designs into quality and well optimized code. I also like to collaborate with others to solve problems and work together as a team.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Address:

No 19B Anuoluwapo Street, Mushin, Lagos, Nigeria.

CONTACT DETAILS

(+234)7017521808

🖾 olatunjiayobami575@gmail.com

Github: haywhyvilla

iii Linkedln: Olatunji-Ayobami

O Twitter: Olatunji-Ayobami

Work Experience

React JS Developer(contract)

BRIDAM Inc. DEC 2022 - PRESENT

- + interpretation of Designs created by the Ui UX Designer
- + Consumption and implementation of APis created by the Backend Developer
- + Development and Management of Multiple Dynamic Web Apps
- + implementation of Git Version Control System

Frontend Developer

FAMESIFY Team, Inc.

APR 2022 - DEC 2022

- + integrate platforms together via third party tools, APis and Webhooks
- + Development and Management of Multiple Dynamic Web Apps
- + Partnered with my team members to assign tasks and follow set guidelines.
- + Responsible for the entire web software mobile responsiveness

Frontend Developer(Intern)

ZURI Team, Inc. AUG 2021 - APR 2022

- + Design Landing Pages and Funnels on various CMS and CRMs
- + Integrate platforms together via third party tools, APIs and Webhooks
- + Partnered with my team members to assign tasks and follow set guidelines.
- + Migrate setup from existing platform to another

Freelance FrontEnd Developer

UPWORK FREELANCE

FEB 2021 - AUG 2021

- + Design responsive and professional e-commerce, real estate, mortgage, etc websites
- + Optimize website loading speed and fix errors on the website.
- + Redesign existing website to improve UI and increase conversion.

Education

(B. Sc.) Material Engineering

UNIVERSITY OF IBADAN

2015 - 2021

Skills

HTML5

CSS

JavaScrip

SASS

Tailwind

ReactJS

Redux

Git

Githul

. .

Figma